# 大家好 前兩天一個網友送了一個這個豬飼料給我們吃
Hi everyone! A couple of days ago, a friend sent a pack, this pack of pig feed for us.
# 哈哈~等一下 哦不是
Ha ha~ Wait! Oh, no!
# 給小豬吃
I mean for the piglets.
# 就在上面 我去餵一下它 看它吃不吃
They're right up there. Let me feed them with it and see if they like it.
# 今天不是餵的酒糟
I'm not giving you distiller grains today.
# 不要激動
Don't be too excited.
# 這個母豬很喜歡吃哦
The sow likes it so much.
# 小豬在那裡
The piglets are over there.
# 好怕
They're scared.
# 你看 小豬那麼大啦
Look! The piglet is that big now.
# 幹嘛 抱一下你而已啊 是不是
What happened? I'm just hugging you, right?
# 給你東西吃你不要 硬要我來抓你 是不是
I gave you food but you didn't take any. You asked for my catching, didn't you?
# 牙齒都長出來啦 該吃點東西啦
Your teeth are already coming out. You should start eating something.
# 不能老吃奶
You can't have only milk all the time.
# 等下我要烤了你呦 那麼兇幹嘛
Bet I'm gonna have you roasted. Why are you that fierce?
# 你是笑還是叫 你看
Are you laughing or screaming? Look!
# 它笑 它在狂笑
It's laughing. It's laughing crazily.
# 逃不脫我的掌心嗎
You can't escape from my hands, can you?
# 我以為是公豬來了 壞我一大跳
I thought the boar was coming. It scared me.
# 誒呦 那麼不配合
Ayo! You're so uncooperative.
# 看你還敢不敢
See if you still dare.
# 沒掙扎了吧
You can't struggle anymore, can you?
# 在笑
It's laughing.
# 那麼兇幹嘛 等下把你閹了
Why are you that fierce? I'm gonna have you castrated.
# 就這樣 把它閹了
Yeah, right! Have it castrated.
# 還是算了 太殘忍了 做不出來
Well, forget it. It's too cruel. I can't make it.
# 把它放了 把它放了
I release it. I release it.
# 去去去 去你老媽那裡
Go, go, go! Go to you mom!
# 這公豬
The boar...
# 那是斷奶的料 你也去吃
You're eating your children's weaning meal.
# 撒在這裡 等下豬下來了
I spray it here, so that the piglets can have a few licks,
# 它看到了它就慢慢地會舔一點 吃一點
or a few bites when they come down and see the feed.
# 這些豬都是 壞的[SIC]很
These pigs are really really naughty.
# 可以吃的 都不敢過來吃
It's food! They don't dare to come.
# 小豬不敢過來吃
The piglets don't dare to come.
# 留下點 留一點明天吃
Leave some, leave some for tomorrow.
# 好啦
Alright!
# 今天的視頻就到這裡啦
The video ends here.